Guide to the Korean American Students of Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Korean American Students of Yale records
1992-1996
RU 871
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of membership lists, charter, printed matter, news articles, and notes documenting the activities and operations of the Korean American Students of Yale (KASY), an undergraduate Yale organization. Also included are the rcords of the Korean-American Intercollegiate Network (KIN).
Korean American Students of Yale
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of membership lists, charter, printed matter, news articles, and notes documenting the activities and operations of the Korean American Students of Yale (KASY), an undergraduate Yale organization. Also included are the rcords of the Korean-American Intercollegiate Network (KIN).
Asian American students -- Societies, etc.; College students -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Records of the Korean-American Intercollegiate Network, 1995-1996; Accession 2001-A-148
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - Charters (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - History (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Membership/contact lists (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - KASCON X -KIN Delegates Assembly (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - KASCON VIII/IX -KIN Delegates Assembly (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Samsung Internship -KIN/MIRAE (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Records of the Korean American Students of Yale, 1992-1993; Accession 2001-A-149
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - Charter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Membership list, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Events (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - East Rock Inst. Conference (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Donation to Korean American Inter-Agency Council (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Korean American Journal (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AASA/KASY news, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Officers, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)